-Encoded by LEET-
(police radio)
Still no sign, over.
I'm going to try that down.
(Dog growling)
SIRN.
Hey, is everything okay?
Sorry, just looking for a record.
Well, come on.
We're not gonna see everyone for a while.
Alright, sorry.
By the way, everyone thinks it's cute.
We're matching.
Babe?
Yeah, just give me a sec.
You really agree to go along with this?
Yes, he's excited.
Are you sure it's what you want?
What do you mean?
You know, I loved him, but he hasn't been
that to him in a while.
Aren't you worried about how long it's
been since the two of you have,
like, you know, why
don't you take the job
and find a country boy
who actually fucks you?
Hey.
Oh, sick.
I know you still did music.
Yeah, actually just finishing up a new EP.
Sick.
Hey, you still on the same label?
Probably self-releasing this time.
But, uh, hey, I heard you guys got booked
on the whole Sound Off tour.
That's awesome.
Dude, you gotta get back on the label.
They just booked you on so much stuff.
That's so true.
Yeah, no, I should just get back on the
label.
He's still going through a lot.
Honestly, it's another reason why I think
this move will be good for both of us.
Okay.
This is so exciting.
Do you think he knows?
He has no idea.
You know, we need a guitarist for the
tour.
What, for real?
I figured, you know, with the move,
that you're written off.
Shit.
I mean, I could check in with Millie,
but...
When you started dating my sister,
I thought you might make her cooler.
Instead, she's just made you.
Hey, fuck you, man.
That's cool.
It's just, when I die, I don't want someone
else's life flashing before my eyes.
I'll do it.
The tour.
Oh, that's dope.
Eh, there's a lot of rehearsals.
I'll make it back.
It's not even that far.
And it's so fucking far.
And look, this isn't that big of a deal.
It's just a couple hours away.
He says a prick.
He can't drive.
Hey, who needs to drive in the city?
Obviously, we're, uh, we're gonna miss you
guys a lot.
This insane group is, you know,
it's, uh, it's the family I got.
So?
Um, but I, I'm so proud of Millie.
You are the sweetest, most giving person
I've ever met.
These kids don't even know
how lucky they are to get
someone who actually
cares about their education.
So, uh, yeah, it's, it's all bittersweet.
I'm a little scared,
but, uh, mainly excited
about the next step
in our lives together.
Woo!
Yeah.
That's it.
Okay, relax.
It's just a change of scenery.
Babe.
In front of the people who
mean the most to us, I want
to ask you to spend the
rest of your life with me.
Are you joking?
Um.
Oh.
Yeah, yes, of course, yes.
I, I, I do.
I, I'm sorry.
I fucking suck, okay?
I just, I, I didn't know what was
happening and I froze.
You still want this, right?
It's a little late now, right?
Yeah, it fucking is.
But still, if we don't split now,
it'll only be harder later.
What?
Wait, wait, wait, like split-split?
Is that what you want?
No, of course not.
I don't know.
You've been so distant since, and that's
okay, of course.
It's just, you've never made me feel
unsure before.
Unsure of what?
If we love each other, or if we're just
used to each other.
Hey.
I'm sorry, okay?
Sorry.
I, I think I drank too much.
It's okay.
Hey, hey, I love you, I love you.
I love you too.
Everyone knows you need me more than I
need you.
We laugh about it.
What?
Resenting me doesn't make you less of a
failure.
Why are you saying this?
Can you ask them to leave?
Who?
I can't sleep with them staring at us.
Good morning.
You clearly don't miss the sound of
traffic.
How long you been up?
Not long.
Figured one of these had to have the
coffee machine inside.
Do you think I resent you?
Well, now.
Sorry.
Still half asleep.
Because you're looking at your dream,
girl.
That must be it.
Since you're out here, can you bring
something inside?
Sure.
Yeah.
Oh!
Help!
Oh my goodness.
Don't let me say no!
This is worrying.
Your dad's?
Maybe I could use it to fix the back
porch.
Never let me use that.
Babe, do you smell that?
I'm peeing.
You really don't smell anything?
What's going on?
Babe?
What are you doing?
I found it.
What?
Oh!
Oh, God.
How'd you know to look for that?
Excuse me.
Hi.
Would you bring that from home or take it
from my tin?
What?
Oh, sorry.
I thought that they were just for the
staff.
But I don't have...
Sugar?
No, thank you.
How much trouble am I in?
Oh, God.
Don't mind Carol.
She's possessive of dry old bags on
account of her being one.
It's Mrs. Wilson, right?
Millie.
I'm Jamie.
Welcome.
Thank you.
I gotta say, I was so happy you took this
placement.
Your resume really caught my eye.
You saw that?
Yeah, well, it's part of the hiring
committee.
Wanna sit?
Yeah, I was just thrilled
that someone of your
caliber was interested in
our tiny neck of the woods.
Oh, are you kidding?
I'm excited.
My old school was huge.
Students and staff all lost in the
shuffle.
Here I'm hoping to actually help these
kids as individuals.
Oh, passion!
Almost forgot what that was like.
And you settling in okay?
You and your husband?
Sorry, your wife?
Or... Me and my... God,
boyfriend sounds so immature.
Partner?
My... Tim?
My... Me and my
boy partner, Tim.
Have you, uh... Have
you explored much?
Partners?
Oh, God, no.
No.
No, the area.
Have you... Have you...
Like, where did you move to?
We, uh... We're down
at the end of Pit Road.
This is so predictably small town,
to say this, but I think we're neighbors.
I'm the yellow house on the corner.
Oh, you're kidding.
Yeah.
It's a great spot.
I mean, it's a little ways from town,
but the woods and the trails are amazing.
Well, uh, let me know if, uh, you ever
need someone to show you around.
Yeah.
You and your boy partner.
Sure.
Have a good day.
Bye.
How's it going?
Hey.
Oh, do we have internet?
Uh, guys, coming next week.
Hey, you obviously can't drive me back for
this gig on Thursday, right?
I could take you to the train station.
Okay, yeah, thanks.
I have to learn these parts.
Okay.
Uh, what about tomorrow?
Do you maybe want to do that hike you were
telling me about?
Yeah, that'd be great.
Great.
Okay.
Love you.
Thank you.
Is this it?
I don't know.
Here, this feels short.
Did we miss something?
Yeah, what about that?
Seems pretty overgrown.
Hun, I don't want to be the dumb city folk
who went against nature and lost.
It's marked, we're good.
Babe.
We can always turn back.
It's just... It's so nice out.
Okay, wait, I think it's this way.
Wait, I think it was back there.
Are you sure?
No, are you?
Okay, that way's north.
Okay.
What do we do with that?
I don't know.
I thought it would be helpful.
Okay.
What if we just keep going sort of
southeast-ish?
Can we just sink for a second?
No, no, no, babe.
This looks right.
Come on.
Oh, my God.
Honey.
Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
No!
Oh, God.
Are you okay?
My legs are-Oh, God.
Oh, God.
My phone.
Shit.
Can you call it?
I don't have signal.
Fuck.
My demos were on there.
I'm fine, by the way.
Hey, sorry, you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
You sure?
Okay.
What is this place?
Do you feel that?
It feels... Crowded.
Better get out of here.
What, back into the storm?
What is all this?
We can build a fire.
Wait it out.
Wait it out later.
Does that really matter right now?
How big is this place?
Let me check.
Hello!
Well?
Pretty big.
Honey.
What are you doing?
Remember when we used to watch Man Vs.
Wild?
Yeah, you fucking don't.
Okay.
Thank you.
I am so thirsty.
Yeah, me too.
Is that all we have?
Yeah.
You think that's drinkable?
I'm not drinking it.
Alright, finish this.
What about you?
I found another bottle.
Oh God.
What's that?
The other bottle.
Babe.
I wouldn't.
Man Vs.
Wild, babe.
No, it's fine.
Here.
So, about that later.
When?
Just before the move.
You?
The same.
When we're out of here, we'll both stop
again.
Definitely.
For now, it's a nice distraction from all
the rats that must be down here.
I keep thinking about that thing you found
the other day.
Me too.
Hey.
What happened there?
When I was a kid, my dad comes home one
day and tells me to clean my room.
Because he says there's a smell.
So, I clean it.
Next day, he comes home, says it's still
there.
So, I clean it again.
The day after that, he comes in.
But, this time he's freaking out.
He's like, what is that goddamn smell?
And he just starts tearing my room apart.
But, can't find anything.
At this point, I'm scared because there is
no smell.
You know, I don't know why he's getting so
worked up.
Anyway, I, um, come home from school the
next day.
And I go in my room.
And he's standing there with this wicked
grin.
Because he found it.
It's a dead rat.
It had been nesting above the warm light.
And every time I used that light,
I was cooking it.
But it was so gradual that...
I couldn't even tell that I was breathing
in this...
This rotting carcass every night.
I can't believe I haven't heard that story
before.
I had forgotten all about it until the
night I found them.
And there's this detail that I never told
you.
But I never told anyone about the smell.
But it was worse than that.
It was like a, like a taste.
Like the air was thick.
And it just got worse the closer I got to
their bedroom.
Then I opened the door.
She was smiling at me.
She had woke to find her other half was
gone.
And her brain just snapped.
She couldn't process it.
Still going to bed each night next to
that...
The face.
The adorable smell.
I was standing there choking on the taste
of him.
And she didn't even notice.
It's like me with the rat.
Just breathing him in like fresh air.
I'm sorry.
It's like a window open between our house
and that night.
I'm sorry.
What do you think?
What?
Oh...
Oh... Only you could
sleep in in a wet cave.
Oh.
What time is it?
Oh...
That sucks.
Let's just get home.
But my demos were on there.
I hate you.
No, you don't.
What are you doing?
Well, I'm not doing anything.
What is that?
Wait, stop, stop, stop.
What the fuck?
What is it?
Mildew or something.
Ow.
Ow, that heart.
I know.
What do you want to do?
A fucking test?
A three-legged race?
Sorry, I... Slow, slow.
Oh,
you're pretty impressive in there.
Remember when I found North?
We should head into town.
There's no food in the house.
There used to be rice.
Oh, we haven't exactly budgeted for two
new phones.
But first... What?
Just two minutes.
Babe.
Come on.
I just spent the night in a cave.
Okay.
Please, please, please.
Fine.
All right, but you do me next.
Mm-hmm.
Babe, come on.
Babe.
Tim.
Tim?
Ah!
What?
What the fuck?
I'm sorry.
Oh.
Trying to be funny?
That really hurt.
Honey, you don't look so good.
I'm just really tired.
I'm gonna head into town.
I can come.
No, you just relax.
And maybe take a shower, yeah?
You
dealt with anxiety, panic attacks.
It's possible this is one of those?
No, I don't think so.
How old are you?
We're actually the same age.
See, there's a history of mental illness
in the family.
Your mother... No,
it's nothing like that.
This is different.
I think it's worth discussing what
happened to her.
I've had this conversation before.
I'm not her.
You have someone to talk to.
Family, a therapist, friends.
Yeah, I got friends back in the city.
So locally, it's just your wife?
Partner.
Yeah, it's just her.
You had this dangerous experience.
When you're left alone
in an unfamiliar place,
no one to help if
something were to go wrong.
Anxiety can fixate on a thought like that
and spiral into a physical panic response.
This is technically a
muscle relaxant, meaning
it slows the central
nervous system down.
So even if your brain
starts panicking, your
body relaxes, shutting
down the feedback loop.
Okay?
Yeah.
You know, you two were lucky.
It was that couple that went missing out
there.
What?
When?
There's still posters up.
Biggest news this sound scene for a while.
Bigger than local man water his garden.
I'm serious.
It was a big search and everything.
The Valium?
It's called diazepam now.
All ready for tomorrow?
Huh?
Honey, if you're not feeling well,
maybe you should cancel.
Hey, if I cancel, I can forget about the
tour.
Hey, we didn't get much data, yeah?
Maybe don't use it
all... What are you...
Cruising for chicks online?
You know, people went missing around here
recently.
Really?
Yeah.
Hey, do me a favor when I die.
Please just nuke any and all of my social
media from existence.
I don't want to be
remembered for posting nature
is what home feels
like and getting 23 likes.
They post this and that's it.
Cool.
Great life.
Okay, so if you die tonight, what's your
final post?
You took the plunge.
Aww.
That is so fucking basic.
Why would you tag me in that?
Because all this shit is basic,
Tim.
Nobody cares.
It's just a like my mom can see.
Plus, you love it.
Whatever.
That'd be a sad one to end it on,
though.
Yeah.
What wouldn't be?
BRB?
Dying.
Literally, who could that be?
Hi.
Hello!
I hope you don't mind.
I was in the neighborhood and,
uh, because I am the neighborhood.
Uh, and I thought I would officially
welcome you to said neighborhood.
Hey.
Hey, man.
Oh, babe.
This is Mr. McCabe.
Jamie, who I told you I am.
Right.
Oh, yeah.
Hey.
You must be Tim, the boy partner.
Nice to meet you.
I'm hoping you drink red.
Oh, Tim drinks anything.
Please come in.
Oh, no, no.
I don't want to intrude.
Mr. McCabe.
I insist you intrude.
Alright.
Thanks.
Here, just to the left.
Mr. McCabe.
That's terrifying.
Well, it was more just the rain.
It was pouring rain.
Right.
I mean, we were totally disoriented.
Well, you know your phone has a compass.
Yeah.
Alright, let's not get stuck on who had
which cardinal directions.
Seriously, though, have you ever seen
anything like that out there?
I was getting, like, cult vibes.
Cult vibes?
Honey, I don't know about that.
Well, were we not in the same place?
It was a cave, but there was, like,
a giant bell and church pews in the walls.
It was fucking weird.
There was a chapel out that way.
Okay.
But that collapsed years ago.
It was just, like, in the middle of
nowhere?
Yeah, it was, like, this new-agey,
hippy-dippy group.
Cold vibes.
What happened to them?
Mass suicide.
No.
Oh, God!
Uh, I don't know.
They just kind of, I don't know,
thinned out over time.
I think they moved on when the weather
took the building.
Hard to recruit new members when your house
of worship becomes a subterranean lair.
I got it.
Thanks, honey.
Yeah.
Man, this food.
I might make a habit of dropping by.
It's all Tim.
I can't cook to save my life, and it's his
fault.
No, it's my fault.
You're so good at this stuff, I've never
had to learn.
So if it weren't for me, you'd know how to
cook?
And if it weren't for
me, you wouldn't be the
only 30-something
without a driver's license.
Well, I have a license.
He doesn't have, he has a learner's
permit.
He can't actually drive a car.
It's a good deal, you know?
She gets a personal cook and I'm trapped
here.
Trapped?
I can't even make it to the train station
unless it fits your schedule.
And nobody's holding you hostage,
Tim.
And now hostages don't have to cook their
own food.
Well, it sounds to me like you complete
each other.
Think?
I mean, that's what
I... It's so weird.
It's... yeah.
Hey, it was nice to meet you, man.
Hey, you too, thanks again.
And I'll see you tomorrow.
Yes, oh, yeah, oh.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
He's friendly.
What?
No, I just, I think he likes you.
No, he doesn't.
Don't be weird.
Mm-hmm.
You seem pretty charmed by him,
too.
Really?
Yeah, you're right.
I might just fall on.
Yeah.
Ow!
Did you just bite me?
No.
What is this?
You're all over me one minute,
and then the next... I didn't.
I just, I...
Something's off.
Ever since we've been here,
I just... Stop with the excuses.
Excuses?
I'm not making this up, babe.
Tim, if you don't want to fuck me,
Tim, just say it.
Mm.
You're on my hair.
Roll over, then you're on my hair.
Tim.
A little pause.
..
You ready?
I don't think you should go.
There's a surprise.
Are we really not going to talk about last
night?
Your acting?
What, crazy?
That's not what I was saying.
I was unconscious, okay?
I didn't know what I was doing.
If you're sick, you should stay home.
Yeah, come on.
I can't miss the train.
Please.
You're going to be great.
You know, I'd drive you the whole way if I
could.
It's fine.
Don't worry about coming back here
tonight.
You mad at me?
No, no, no, no, no.
I just mean stay out.
Enjoy the after party, you know, sleep at
Luke's and actually catch up with everyone.
No use coming back here and feeling
trapped.
I didn't mean that.
Sure, but maybe some space would be good.
Are you sure?
Escape!
Be free!
Okay.
Yeah, you're right.
Thanks.
No, no, no, no.
All right.
Great work, team.
I'll see you after P.E.
Anna, Mr. Richardson won't like it if
you're late.
Sorry, miss.
Are these your dogs?
None anymore.
I don't know.
I, you know, honestly, it's been hard.
Are you okay?
Like, do you need me to come up there?
I, fuck it.
I'm coming up there.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm probably making it sound worse than it
is.
And anyway, my folks are coming up for
lunch on Sunday.
So, yeah, he probably just needs to see a
familiar face.
Yeah, I just want to make sure you're
okay.
I'm fine.
I like the quiet country life.
I'm the boring one.
Yeah.
You think you're boring because what?
You have an actual proper job?
I loved him.
But he is a 35-year-old white guy who
still thinks he's going to be a rock star.
That is fucking boring.
He's a good guy.
Is he?
Yes.
You know, I always think about our first
date.
I said my favorite band was the Spice
Girls.
I didn't realize he was like this music
snob guy.
And then he shows up on our second date
with Spice on vinyl.
That is sweet.
But that was nearly a decade ago.
What has he done lately?
I gonna go.
Why?
No, no, no, no, no.
No!
Where were you doing?
Yes, I need to see you.
Why aren't you on the train?
This is really fucking weird, Tim.
It's like I'm thirsty all over,
but not now.
And not with you.
Me too.
What are we doing?
I'm sorry, I just... I had a feeling.
I don't apologize.
Let's just try it at home next week.
Or maybe don't.
So long.
Okay.
Now you gotta get out of here.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
It's... why... why are you, like,
tensing?
What?
I...
Babe, it's... wait, I'm stuck.
Ow.
It hurts.
I know, I know.
It hurt.
Get out of here now.
I'm trying.
It's not fucking moving.
That hurts.
Thank you.
Listen to me.
I'm sorry.
Everything okay in there?
Just a sec.
Everything okay, Miss Wilson?
Sorry.
I had to, uh...
Miss Wilson.
You know this is, uh...
A bathroom for little boys.
Sorry.
I, uh...
Had to...
Go to class.
Everything's fine.
Next time, try to... Get
to the staff bathroom.
Yeah.
And you might
wanna, uh... Clean up.
Shit.
Babe.
Babe, come on.
We're just not gonna talk about this?
Do you...
Understand what you did today?
I could've been fired.
Or worse, like... Like...
Arrested worse.
Wait, I didn't make you do anything.
You don't fuck me for months, then you barge
into my work with that I need you shit?
Yeah, you kinda did.
God... Are you trying
to ruin this for me?
You know, I have sat on the sidelines.
I have sacrificed so
that you've had space to
try to make your impossible
dreams come true.
Whoa, I'm not gonna apologize for taking
some risks.
And I never can because you use all the
risk up.
I moved here for you.
I left my whole life behind.
What life?
God, your music?
Then why aren't you at your show?
Tim, if you think I've trapped you,
why don't you fucking leave?
I can't.
I don't think I'm okay.
It's like...
My brain and my body aren't talking.
You don't understand.
I guess I don't.
Wait, where are you going?
To clean up your mess?
Sounds familiar?
Do you want me to come?
What do you want, Tim?
I can't make every decision for you.
I'm not your fucking mother.
Even if I'm starting to feel like her.
What's that supposed to mean?
Like I'm living with something that's
dead.
Millie?
Hi.
The yellow house on the corner.
Yeah.
So... Today... I just
wanted to apologize again...
For...
I'm... So embarrassed...
About, um...
Oh, that!
Oh, no.
Don't even mention it.
That's...
Female... Issues.
It's, uh... Please don't... No.
Say no more, please.
Thanks.
Hey!
What's wrong?
Sorry, um... It's just
been a really stressful day.
Tim and I just had a big fight.
Sorry.
This is not your problem.
Wanna come inside?
I don't wanna intrude.
Miss Wilson...
I insist you intrude.
I'll get you a glass of water.
You sure I can't tempt you with anything
stiffer?
Uh, no.
Water's fine, thanks.
What's going on?
Uh... I don't know.
I keep thinking this was a mistake.
Like... Since the move, Tim and
I haven't been on the same page.
But then... Maybe we haven't
been on the same page for a while.
And we're just...
Too scared to admit it.
Do you, uh...
Do you love each other?
Yeah.
Of course.
Right?
But...
I mean, I don't remember life before Tim.
So... Maybe we're
just... Complacent.
Well, you know, complacency can sometimes
simply be harmony.
Do you wanna... Here's something
I teach my ninth grade history class.
Desperately.
Plato wrote that the ancient Greeks
believed we were created with four arms,
four legs, and a head with two faces.
But, uh, Zeus feared our power,
so he split us into two separate parts.
Dooming us to spend our lives in search of
the other half.
If you think you've found that,
don't be so quick to let it go.
Well, if Plato says so.
Is it just you here?
Sorry, that's... it's none of my business.
Oh, no, please, God, I'm the one prying.
Uh, yeah, there were two of us when we
first bought this place.
Uh, and we were probably, you know,
around the same age as you guys.
Probably had the same issues, same fights.
And there was a brief time where I
actually did walk away.
And it was liberating.
I had the freedom to do whatever I wanted.
So what did you do?
Oh, nothing.
I was miserable.
Yeah, I just didn't know how to exist on
my own.
I even started to miss the fights we had.
Yeah, for better or worse, I was me
because of him.
I bet you miss him.
You know, I have a tape of my wedding that
I have been looking for an excuse to...
Uh, you know, that sounds great,
but I should head back.
Thanks.
Next time.
Sorry.
Sorry, okay, I didn't know where else to
go.
Babe, you ready for bed?
Babe?
Are you asleep?
I'm sorry.
I wish I could be what either of us wants
me to be.
Mill?
Oh shit.
Babe!
Baby, baby, wake up.
Wake up.
Millie, wake up!
Baby!
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
Maybe it was like a seizure.
A seizure?
Since when have you had seizures?
Or sleepwalked?
It's probably stress and you're not
helping.
Look, I think something happened to me in
the cave.
Something that's making me act insane.
And now it's like... it's like it's in you
too.
Alright, that missing
couple, those hikers, they
were on the same path
that took us to the cave.
What if whatever happened to them is
happening to us?
I feel fine.
But that's because you're awake.
You're adrenalized, okay?
I think it gets worse at night.
It's like when the mind gets tired,
the body can take over.
Listen to what you're saying.
Alright, remember that morning our legs
stuck together?
You said that was just mildew.
Since when do I know anything about
mildew?
I don't even know what it fucking is!
After we had sex, we couldn't separate.
Explain that.
It had been a while.
That always makes it a little painful.
Pain.
Okay, alright, put your hand up like this.
Try not to touch mine.
You'll feel it, babe, please.
This is ridiculous.
I'm going to bed.
Come on, it's like we're magnetic,
babe, please.
I think you should sleep in the spare room
tonight.
I agree.
We need to keep our distance.
Babe, wait.
I know why you stopped.
Because the moment you got there,
I wanted you to stop.
I felt it.
That's not...
It's... That doesn't
make any sense.
Then how come I know exactly what you're
feeling?
The pull?
The thirst in your bones?
Babe, something inside us has imprinted on
each other.
We're sick, okay?
I can't explain it, but it's that place.
It has to be.
Tim... We need answers.
I'm gonna go back.
Go back.
Yeah, as soon as there's light,
I'll go.
You know my parents are coming for lunch
Sunday?
Yeah, why?
I...
I don't think you should be here.
What does that mean?
It means... I don't want you...
I don't want you.
I love you.
What is that?
I don't want you to...
I don't want you
to... Thank God.
What is happening?
Fight it.
Baby, you've got to fight it.
I just want to die.
Baby, look at me.
Stay with me, we can do this.
Honey, do what?
The drugs, the pills, the drugs.
What?
Muscle relaxes!
Valium, Valium!
It's called diazepam now.
What do you child want?
Hold it out.
Help me!
Take him!
Okay, okay, quicker if we snort him.
Oh, shit!
Oh!
Yeah, just put your feet against mine and
then push away.
I can't do it!
Baby, yes, you can!
You're so fucking strong you can do it!
I pushed me.
We only need to last a couple minutes.
I'm pushing!
We got this!
I can do it!
Just keep pushing!
Keep pushing!
Just keep pushing.
I was hoping I'd have more time before you
woke up.
It's gonna be okay.
What's going on?
Sorry, we don't have time for you to hem
and haw about this.
About what?
Well, babe, it's a weird time for a joke.
It's not getting worse, so the drugs must
still be in our system, right?
Wait.
Wait, wait, babe, babe.
I wasn't even sure that was the right tool
to fix the fucking Porsche.
Listen, when the pills wear off,
it's gonna start again.
No, babe, babe, babe, babe.
Imagine what you're about
to do actually happening,
and tell me that's not gonna
make things way worse!
Whiskey for the pain.
And as soon as we're separated,
I'll sprint for the first aid kit.
We have bandages, disinfectant,
everything we need!
Oh, you're right-handed.
Oh, God!
Actually, maybe that's enough of that.
Why, why?
I think I can feel your whiskey.
You're right-handed and drunk!
Remember when you said you weren't holding
me hostage?
Do you think I wanna do this?
No!
Don't!
We are out of time!
No, no!
We need to do this while the joke is in
our system.
Then we can get help.
I'm sorry.
We have to.
If we don't split now, it'll be much
harder later.
There's gotta be another way!
Do
it.
Do it.
Okay.
Careful, careful!
Alright, I'm doing it.
I'm doing it.
By the way, I'm sorry I didn't believe you
before.
You were right, obviously.
Babe, just go!
I wanna go.
A doctor isn't gonna be able to fix this!
Get in the trunk.
We need to keep as much distance as
possible.
Honey, the pills are gonna wear off-I
know, but more pills!
It's just a bandaid!
We need answers!
Kim!
I just sawed through our fucking arms!
We are going to the hospital!
Okay.
Shit.
What?
What's going on?
My keys.
I think I left them at Jamie's.
Why would you do that?
I didn't do it on purpose!
Sorry.
Come on.
You coming?
I'll wait.
Like you said, distance.
Tim, don't do anything stupid.
Jamie?
I'm so sorry.
It's me.
I'm just...
Sorry.
We need help.
It's... It's serious shit.
Jamie?
Hello?
The happiest day of our life.
I'll give these back.
Don't worry.
What is this?
The beginning of something wonderful.
Help me!
Stay away from me.
We were scared at first, too.
Everybody is.
But this is a great gift.
Such lucky few are we who become whole.
No.
I don't want this.
Oh, but you do.
The connection is deeper than anything you
could ever imagine.
No more walls.
Share fears and memories.
This is the hardest part.
You just have to push through.
Please.
What awaits is the ultimate intimacy in
divine flesh.
Stop it!
It's already happening.
You wouldn't like the alternative.
Help me!
Billy!
Rejoice in the intimacy that awaits.
No dissonance.
Only warmth.
I'm sorry, but it's best to be open for
each other.
It will hurry things along.
The God's jealousy has robbed you of your
perfect form.
Yet divine happiness is flowing through
us.
You will be so warm.
geometry Buggy I know, I know.
This thing, it's happened before,
we're not the first.
I know.
You went there.
I saw something down there.
I think I know how to stop it.
We can't fight it forever.
No!
Stay back!
It's okay.
You can let go.
Oh, honey, I'm serious.
Don't come any closer.
No.
There's only one way to end this.
What are you doing?
What I should have done a long time ago.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Babe, I used to worry I wouldn't remember
who I was without you.
But the truth is, I remember exactly who I
was.
Okay, I was miserable.
I was incomplete.
Cold.
So much time wasted
thinking about some other life
where all my bullshit
adolescent dreams came true.
But... Babe, you are
the dream that came true.
I'm so sorry it took me so long, but I
just... I fucking suck and I love you so much.
I love you so much.
Close your eyes.
What?
Trust me, close your eyes.
Tim, what are you doing?
This won't end until one of us is dead,
okay?
Babe, I don't want you to see this.
We don't have time, okay?
No, you don't have to.
You don't have to.
It's gonna be okay.
You'll be okay.
Babe, please just drop it.
Just drop it.
Please, just drop it.
Babe, babe, babe, babe, babe.
Oh, shit.
Oh, God.
Baby, baby, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, stay with me, baby.
Hey, yes, yeah, hey, hey.
You gotta run.
You gotta be free.
I'll never be free from you.
Baby, I'll never.
Promise me one thing.
Anything.
You'll make my final post vrb dying.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, Millie,
Millie, no, no, hey, Millie, Millie!
Shit, baby, baby, baby, stay with me,
please, please!
No, no, no, baby!
What have you done?
It's the only way to stop the bleeding.
What?
No.
No, no.
I was trying to let you go.
Did you want to let me go?
What are you doing?
It's your favorite album, right?
Do you remember that?
I always imagined it as our first dance,
but... Because maybe that won't happen now.
Are you sure you want this?
I do.
Say you believe it.
Free your mind without a danger.
Leave the real, don't be a stranger.
We can achieve it.
Come a little bit closer, baby.
Get it on.
Cause tonight... I love you.
I love you too.
When to become love.
I need some love.
Like I never needed love before.
One week in love to you, baby.
I had a little love.
Now I'm back for more.
One week in love to you, baby.
Set your spirit free.
It's the only way to be.
I'm back.
Oh my god!
Your
restless heart and
your money I see you on my restless screen
You're scrolling by another You're not
another one, you're mine You're not
another one,
you're mine Hello, hello,
oh-oh-oh-oh The
empty cup, the open womb
Praise be to this useless love Next to all
we ever loved.
Another.
You're not another one, you're mine.
You're mine.
All that time.
Gone forever.
Only sky.
All that money.
All that time.
Climbed in heaven.
Orange, every pint.
You are not another one.
You're mine.
You're not another one.
POLLOCK